FAIZAN HAIDER

Network Administrator





+92-311-0086555 🖆 Faizanhaiderofficial@outlook.com

EDUCATION

Master of Computer Science **National College of Business Administration** 2021

EXPERTISE

- Network Administration
- System Administration
- Surveillance

INTERPERSONAL SKILL

- Management Skills
- Critical Thinking
- Communication Skills

LANGUAGE

- English
- Urdu

PROFILE

I want to become an effective Network Engineer have the Technical Expertise and positive attitude necessary to be successful in any transaction i intend to learn more about this in future this contribute to my recognition in the associated field i'll continuously update my knowledge and use it to advance the organization

WORK EXPERIENCE

Masood Textile Mill Pvt.Ltd

2012-2018

Assistant Officer Surveillance

- · Install and set up Cameras DVR,NVR and IP Base Equipment and online connectivity
- · Monitor Live video feeds and review recorded footage to identify security breaches, Suspicious activities and incidents
- configure camera setting resolution and angles to optimize video quality

Sufi Weaving industries Pvt.Ltd

2018-2020

System Support Engineer

- · install configure and maintain system infrastructure such as server, client operating system and wireless connectivity to ensure secure and effective operation
- Monitor,control and uphold network infrastructure Router Switches,Surveillance and Access points
- maintain documentation of system configuration and security Procedure and
- manage User group policies and user permission and troubleshoot issues
- Provide Microsoft Office and outlook Support to end user

Beacon Impex Pvt.Ltd

2020-Present

Assistant Manager Network

- install, configure and monitor hardware and software such as Router, Switches firewall, Access points and Surveillance System
- Monitor network infrastructure and provide end user highly available connectivity
- Manage document of network configuration hardware inventory and Network
- Plan design and implement latest updates on devices and ensure effective communication

REFERENCES

· Will be on demand